<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io</link>
    <atom:link href="http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 00:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 00:45:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Community Events</title>
      <link>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/2014/02/04/upcoming-community-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author></author>
      <guid>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/2014/02/04/upcoming-community-events</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mark your calendar for the following upcoming community events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;march_4th_at_700pmmarch_community_meeting&quot;&gt;March 4th at 7:00pm—March Community Meeting&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the Severna Park Baptist Church on Benfield Blvd. See the upcoming agenda on the front page. Feel free to come with any important community related questions, concerns, or ideas as well as meet some new neighbors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;march_8th_from_9am12nooncmia_key_day&quot;&gt;March 8th from 9am—12noon—CMIA Key Day&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All CMIA Gate Keys and Parking Stickers will change in 2014: At the Severna Park Baptist Church on Benfield Blvd. Gate locks are scheduled to be changed on May 1st. Please see pages 2 and 3 for more information and an application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;march_11th_at_700pmcmia_book_club_meeting&quot;&gt;March 11th at 7:00pm—CMIA Book Club Meeting&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our current selection is Still Life with Bread Crumbs by Anna Quinlen. Anyone is welcome and if you are interested, please contact Kristin Silva at ka_silva@verizon.net for more details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;april_26thcommunity_beautification_work_day&quot;&gt;April 26th—Community Beautification Work Day&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call for participation: Grab your gloves, shovels and community pride! This is a great event for all ages and a way to help school age kids understand the value of community spirit. Activities may include debris removal, weeding and planting flowers at our community properties. Contact Lisa Bender 410.544.4874 for more information. Can’t participate on work day? Consider taking a family “trash” walk around the neighborhood and collecting trash along the way. Let us know what you or your family did at CMIAkids@gmail.com and we’ll include you in our next newsletter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;may_10th_from_8am2pmannual_community_yard__plant_sale&quot;&gt;May 10th from 8am-2pm—Annual Community Yard &amp;amp; Plant Sale&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call for participation: Either set up at your house or join us near Sign Island at the old clubhouse property. We will advertise in the papers and put out signs. We will have two community tables at Sign Island: a plant table and a white elephant table filled with your donations. Dividing your perennials this year? Cleaning out the garage? Donate your extras to CMIA. If you plan to have a yard sale that day, you can register your location on the website or send an email toCarri585@earthlink.net. We will be handing out a list of participating homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;june_3rd_at_700pmjune_community_meeting&quot;&gt;June 3rd at 7:00pm—June Community Meeting&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the Severna Park Baptist Church on Benfield Blvd. The upcoming agenda will be in the Summer 2014 news- letter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;tbdcommunity_and_pier_work_day&quot;&gt;TBD—Community and Pier Work Day&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Details will be announced at Key Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;tbdcmia_annual_community_picnic&quot;&gt;TBD—CMIA Annual Community Picnic&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This an nual fun-filled event will be scheduled for September 2014. 2013’s picnic was a blast….good food, rocking music, great prizes, fantastic friends!!! Start looking forward to the fun now!!! Details in the next newsletter. If you would like to help coordinate this annual event, please come to the March community meeting with your ideas. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;cmia_family_fun_nights&quot;&gt;CMIA Family Fun Nights&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Family friendly volleyball evenings will be returning this spring as soon as weather permits. Watch for details at Sign Island and join us. If you want to help, contact Bo Dant at 410- 544-9556 but definitely come out and have some fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;cmia_preschoolers_playgroup&quot;&gt;CMIA Preschoolers’ Playgroup&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in taking over the CMIA Preschoolers Playgroup, please contact Beth Straub at bifh@netscape.net. Beth will no longer be organizing the playgroup.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from our President</title>
      <link>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/2014/02/03/a-note-from-our-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author></author>
      <guid>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/2014/02/03/a-note-from-our-president</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is almost spring and if you think like me, you are longing to get outside to play. Please look inside the Spring 2014 issue of the Eagle for some important community announcements. You’ll also find news about the following upcoming community events such as the annual CMIA key day, yard and plant sale, and Easter egg hunt. We are also currently planning for the community beautification/planting day.. Volunteers are always needed. More details are inside. Additionally, we are thinking about entering a float in the annual Severna Park July 4th parade — we just need people to organize it. Plan on coming to the next community meeting to learn about and/or volunteer for any of these activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please- all our community activities, projects and events need your support. The Board is only a handful of people and we are trying to keep the “Improvement” in C-M-I-A, but WE NEED YOU to be successful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As winter warms up into spring- we have the ‘ever repeated’ reminders: Do a little bit to clean up some winter waste around the neighborhood. &lt;strong&gt;DRIVE SAFE AND SLOW&lt;/strong&gt; - watch out for all our residents — small and tall — that are starting to come out and play. Help to keep Carrollton Manor a safe and happy place to live. I look for- ward to seeing you at the March 4th meeting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Handling of Yard Waste</title>
      <link>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/2014/02/02/handling-of-yard-waste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author></author>
      <guid>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/2014/02/02/handling-of-yard-waste</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spring is on its way!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that said, yard waste and tree trimmings should be composted or placed at the curb for pick up, not dumped on CMIA Community Property. You may think it is only leaves, but it builds up into debris and becomes trash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have been working hard to beautify our neighborhood. Anything dumped on East Drive, Severn Rd, Park Rd, and the woods at Hillbottom can become our responsibility to cleanup. The community has had to deal with, and sometimes pay for, the removal of leaves, yard trash, and tree branches on community property or in the woods.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CMIA Key and Parking Sticker Day</title>
      <link>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/2014/02/01/cmia-key-and-parking-sticker-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author></author>
      <guid>http://carrolltonmanor.github.io/2014/02/01/cmia-key-and-parking-sticker-day</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CMIA Key and Parking Sticker Day is &lt;strong&gt;Saturday, March 8th, 9:00am - 12:00pm&lt;/strong&gt;, at the Severna Park Baptist Church Fellowship Hall, 506 Benfield Road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All CMIA gate keys and parking stickers will expire this year! New keys and parking stickers will be good for 2 years. All community property locks will be changed on May 1, 2014. To avoid being locked out of Hillbottom Beach, the boat ramp &amp;amp; pier, as well as CrabAway Pier, please make every effort to stop by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year the application is included in this newsletter (see facing page) to expedite the process. Please bring all necessary paperwork and documentation to Key Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;gate_keys__parking_stickers&quot;&gt;Gate Keys &amp;amp; Parking Stickers&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Complete in full the application on page 3 The cost for CMIA keys remain the same: Black gate keys: (Hillbottom Beach/Crabaway pier) - $5.00 Boat ramp - $20.00 Parking stickers - $1.00 Please try to get your keys now - after key day, keys will be available only at CMIA community meetings or by appointment only. Appointments can arranged by calling Lillian Serio at 410-647-5450, ONLY on weekday evenings between 6:00pm- 9:00pm. Please do not call at other times. You will need to bring your driver’s license or a form of ID as proof of Carrollton Manor residency. You will also need to bring your car registration showing your tag number for purchase of stickers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;canoe_rack_lottery&quot;&gt;Canoe Rack Lottery&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applications for the canoe rack lottery will be available at the upcoming March 4th Community Meeting and on Key Day at the Severna Park Baptist Church Fellowship Hall. Canoes and watercraft without an assigned slip or rack will be considered “abandoned” and will be removed from any community properties. Once assigned a rack, all canoes must be secured when not in use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    

  </channel> 
</rss>